ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 1 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 21)
  Includes: Pauline Newman sews as group including Stulberg look on; Union Label press conference, 12/22/59; Meany and Gus Tyler look at book, 1960; ILGWU representatives receive the Moral Tone in Advertising award, 1960; Antonini, Zimmerman, Wagner, Lehman, Uviller, David Dubinsky, Nelson Rockefeller and Hochman watch Mrs. Nelson Rockefeller sew in first Union Label, 1/9/59; women in front of Union Label display; Conn. manager Bert Cooper presents Union Label Apron to Gov. Abraham Ribicoff, Aug. 1960; Union Label advertisement on subway; close up of a Union Label; Moe Rosen changes Times Square street sign to "Union Label Square", 9/1/60; Julia Balasz distributes ILGWU Union Label aprons, June 1960; Stulberg and Antonini watch Newark's governor's wife sew in a Union Label
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 2 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 3 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 1 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Includes: Stulberg watches woman sew in Union Label; Meany and Eisenhower; ILGWU women in front of a huge Christmas tree; group including Antonini, Wagner, Lehman, Uviller, Nelson Rockefeller, and David Dubinsky watch Mrs. Nelson Rockefeller sew in the first Union Label; men make Union Label t shirts; women on Union Label parade float; Stulberg with a little girl, Union Label posters in the background, June 1965; women on parade float, 12/7/60; little girls hold a Union Label poster; little Asian girl in a Union Label kimono; Local 295 Pittston Union Label Committee; Sol Chaikin at a Union Label display, Springfield, Illinois, 1975; black women hold Union Label banner; chorus singing, 1977; exhibit showing work rooms of 1900 and 1960; booth at Denver Union Label show; people at the Capitol, Sept. 1979; ILGWU fashion show; billboard advertising Union Label; ILGWU women distribute leaflets; airplane with Union Label banner behind it; women in dresses covered with the Union Label; David Dubinsky and Esther Peterson; Edward Koch with ILGWU women in Rockefeller Center, New York City, 1979; David Dubinsky at opening of Union Label Advertising Campaign, Grand Central Station, June, 1961; woman carrying a Union Label shopping bag, 1963; Chaikin speech at fashion show; Chaikin and Stulberg with girls in Union Label dresses; Stulberg with women in Union Label dresses; images from production of Union Label television commercial, 1979; Meany and Eisenhower; David Dubinsky runs sewing machine as Meany looks on
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 2 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 3 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 4 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 5 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 6 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 7 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 8 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 9 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 10 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 11 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 12 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 13 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Union Label (see also: Bx. 50 ff 25) [folder 14 of 14] (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Union Label - Mass. (Box 41, Folder 14a)
  Includes: Union men and women distribute Union Label leaflets
- Union Label - Pennsylvania (Box 41, Folder 14b)
  Includes: woman hands out leaflets outside a store
- Unions - selected (Box 41, Folder 15)
  Includes: Rockettes on strike in front of Radio City Music Hall, 1967; group of Frackville strikers meeting, 1933
- Unions [folder 1 of 2] (Box 41, Folder 16)
  Includes: ILGWU administrator Cornelius Wall gives a check to Caesar Chavez; Rockettes picket outside Radio City Music Hall, 1967; Caesar Chavez holds a sign urging a boycott of Iceberg Lettuce; Machinists Union District 27 members picket, Louisville, Kentucky; George Meany speaks behind podium bearing presidential seal, as Eisenhower claps for him; Meany looks at poster for 1960 AFL-CIO Union Industries Show; Stulberg and Potofsky, Stulberg talks at podium bearing Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Symbol, as Potofsky looks on; David Dubinsky at Convention of Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers; United Steelworkers of America meeting; large group of men in suits including Meany, Potofsky, and David Dubinsky; David Dubinsky - speech, as Harry Van Arsdale and others look on; David Dubinsky with William Schnitzler and Daniel Conway; David Dubinsky - speech; David Dubinsky at banquet to celebrate the union of the Bakers Union and Cake Bakers Union, 3/20/73
- Unions [folder 2 of 2] (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Unity House - selected [folder 1 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 18)
  Includes: folk dancing; women on porch of Unity House, Cape Cod, Mass.; swimming on Unity Lake; men and women playing badminton; Meany and Goldberg; cutting the ribbon at the theater, with Meany, David Dubinsky, Antonini, Stulberg, and Zimmerman; Unity House staff, 7/1/61; group at discussion on the economic basis of modern civilization, 1928; group at lecture on appreciation of art, 7/5/25; discussion on Social Psychology, Aug. 1926; discussion on Social Interpretation of Literature, Aug. 1926; Aerial photo of Unity House; house on fire; men watching house on fire; building at Unity House; cabins in the woods; women talk in the woods; Hochman, David Dubinsky, Hanna Haskel, and Antonini dine with others; group including David Dubinsky and Zimmerman listen to a lecture by Jan Valtin; women talk over a Coca-Cola; men play shuffleboard; people at the lakefront
- Unity House - selected [folder 2 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Unity House - selected [folder 3 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 1 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Includes: bosses "picket" David Dubinsky's table at a dinner; David Dubinsky at opening of Unity House, 6/3/38; Drawing of plans for the theater; David Dubinsky, Antonini in group in front of new theater; folk dancing; swimming on Unity lake; bosses point at David Dubinsky during a song; Unity House from the sky; photo of building model; cabins (color); Unity House entrance; Asian person rows a boat; playing volleyball; Lakeside Recreation Hall & Theater; theater; barber shop; cabins; bungalows; ice cream parlor; kitchen; Molisani, David Dubinsky, Angela Bambace, and Antonini with bust of Giuseppe Mazzini; David Dubinsky in front of theater; large group of men including David Dubinsky; group including David Dubinsky, Zimmerman listen to Jan Valtin; construction of a new building, 7/22/71
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 2 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 3 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 4 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 5 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 6 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 7 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Unity House (see also: Bx. 50 ff 26 and #5780/49 - Box 11 ff 8-11) [folder 8 of 8] (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Unity House - Caricature Mural [folder 1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 8a)
  Includes: caricatures of: Edward Murrow; Zeppo Marx; Catherine Hepburn; Harpo Marx; Frank Sinatra; Groucho Marx; May West; Charlie Chaplin; Alfred Hitchcock; Mickey Mouse; Laurel and Hardy; Bob Hope; Jack Benny; James Cagney; Lucile Ball; Marlena Dietrich; Clark Gable; Greta Garbo; and others
- Unity House - Caricature Mural [folder 2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 8b)
- Unity House - Collected by Frannie Shapiro (Box 42, Folder 8c)
  Includes: older photos of groups of vacationers; group including David Dubinsky
- Unity House [folder 1 of 5] (Box 42, Folder 8d)
  Lederer family albums of Forest Park Hotel, 1905-1910, which were purchased by ILGWU in 1919 and became Unity House
- Unity House [folder 2 of 5] (Box 42, Folder 8e)
- Unity House [folder 3 of 5] (Box 42, Folder 8f)
- Unity House [folder 4 of 5] (Box 42, Folder 8g)
- Unity House [folder 5 of 5] (Box 42, Folder 8h)
- Upper South Department - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 9)
  Includes: Antonini, Meany, and Bambace at ILGWU 29th Convention, 1956; Bambace; Bambace - speech; parade float; women waving; women strikers; group photo including Kreindler and Haskel
- Upper South Department - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Upper South Department [folder 1 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 11)
  Includes: Humphrey - speech, Stulberg in background; Bombace - speech; striking women; sign congratulating Sol Chaikin; Meany and Bambace; black man striking; cutter with his machine; group including Bambace; picketing Judy Bond; Chaikin speaking; women march in parade, c. 1950`s; Bambace with women in Union Label dresses; girls point to the union charter; children at Welfare party, Baltimore, 12/20/57; Hannah Haskell, Charles Kreindler, and Angela Bambace, July 1950; Local 1109 members on strike; Bambace, Kreindler, and Zimmerman; Kreindler - speech, as Bambace looks on; women of the Maiden Form softball team, Princeton, New Jersey; Chaikin speaks as Bambace looks on; Bambace - speech; Local 561 members strike; Kreindler, Haskell, and David Dubinsky in group; Kreindler with women in Union Label dresses; bus on way to 1950 Convention; Zimmerman, with a large bandage on his head, and David Dubinsky; Stulberg at his desk; people clap for LBJ; LBJ waves to crowd; Sen. Robert C. Bird; Sen. John Butler; Rep. John R. Foley; Foley with Kreindler and Bambace; Rep. Edward Garmatz; women with political posters; political scene in With These Hands; Kreindler and Bambace speak; Bambace with Zimmerman; Christmas tree at Welfare Party, Baltimore, 12/20/57; Kenrose Mfg strike, 1960; Local 420 members on a parade float; a crowd goes wild as Angela Bambace is nominated for another term; strikers outside Sears; Zimmerman, Stulberg, Bambace, and Kreindler; Bambace talks to women; Bambace, John Martin, and Agnes Martin, 1950; Kreindler and Bambace; Quality Mgr.. Co. workers strike; group including Bambace holds charter, 1950; Bambace with A. Philip Randolph; Local 438 members on a parade float; Rep. Edward Gamatz with women in Union Label dresses; party at Local 422's 10th Anniversary; delegates on boardwalk at 1950 convention
- Upper South Department [folder 2 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Upper South Department [folder 3 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Upper South Department [folder 4 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Upper South Department [folder 5 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Upper South Department [folder 6 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Upper South Department [folder 7 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Upper South Department [folder 8 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Upper South Department [folder 9 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Upper South Department [folder 10 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Upper South Department [folder 11 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Upper South Department [folder 12 of 12] (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Upper South Department [folder 1 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 1)
  Includes: picketers; parade float; employees of Claire Frocks on a parade float; Bambace - speech; strikers rest in the shade; group photo including David Dubinsky, Bambace, and women in Union Label dresses; Kreindler; black woman and black man striking; G.H. & E. Freydberg workers on strike; Sherritt Flag workers strike; Katzenberg strikers; Local 561 members strike; Local 403 members strike Ace Mfg; Forge Mfg workers strike; striker campfire; float advertising Unity House; Binstron workers strike; Local 400 members strike; Bambace speaks with her portrait in the background; black striker takes a break to sit down; strikers picket Sears; Baltimore Sun papers Unit strikes; women in historical dress with their parade float; Kreindler - speech; Gus Tyler, Kreindler, and David Dubinsky; David Dubinsky - speech, as Kreindler looks on; delegates of Locals from the Upper South Dept. at the 1950 Convention; woman at her sewing machine; Claire Frock workers on strike, Thurmont, Maryland, 1950; women in Union Label dresses in front of a huge Union Label; David Dubinsky with Joint Board Retirees; Upper South Dept. Conference, Roanoke, Virginia, 1951; the Committee on Resolutions, 1950 convention; David Dubinsky - speech
- Upper South Department [folder 2 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Upper South Department [folder 3 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Upper South Department [folder 4 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Upper South Department [folder 5 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Upper South Department [folder 6 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Upper South Department [folder 7 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Upper South Department [folder 8 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Upper South Department [folder 9 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Upper South Department [folder 10 of 10] (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 1 of 5] (Box 43, Folder 11)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini; Shelly Appleton; Angela Bambace; Morris Bialis; Joseph Breslaw; David Dubinsky; Evelyn Dubrow; Moe Falikman; David Gingold; Harry Greenburg; Julius Hochman; Louis Hyman; Mattie Jackson; Benjamin Kaplan; Nicolas Kirtzman; Abraham Kirzner; Edward Kramer; Philip Kramer; Charles Kreindler; Samuel Lefkovits; Jennie Matyas; Isadore Nagler; Louis Nelson; Salvatore Ninfo; Samuel Otto; Julio Ramirez; E.J. Rihrer; William Ross; George Rubin; Bernard Shane; Louis Stulberg; Cornelius Wall; Charles Zimmerman
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 2 of 5] (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 3 of 5] (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 4 of 5] (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 5 of 5] (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 1)
  see above listing for Bx. 43, f. 11-15
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members [folder 1 of 3] (Box 44, Folder 3)
  Includes: different photos of those listed in Bx. 43
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members [folder 2 of 3] (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Vice Presidents and Executive Board Members [folder 3 of 3] (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Vice Presidents & General Executive Board Portraits - selected (Box 44, Folder 6)
  Includes: portraits of people from Bx. 43, f. 11-15
- Vice Presidents & General Executive Board Portraits [folder 1 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 7)
  See Bx. 43, f. 11-15
- Vice Presidents & General Executive Board Portraits [folder 2 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Vice Presidents - selected (Box 44, Folder 9)
  Includes: photos of those listed in Bx. 43, f. 11-15
- Vice Presidents [folder 1 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Vice Presidents [folder 2 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Vice Presidents [folder 3 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Vice Presidents [folder 4 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Vice Presidents Speaking [folder 1 of 6] (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Vice Presidents Speaking [folder 2 of 6] (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Vice Presidents Speaking [folder 3 of 6] (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Vice Presidents Speaking [folder 4 of 6] (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Vice Presidents Speaking [folder 5 of 6] (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Vice Presidents Speaking [folder 6 of 6] (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Visitors, International (Box 44, Folder 20)
  Includes: Visiting Swedish Trade Unionists with Hochman, Mark Starr, and Stulberg, in front of mural, 1959; woman from India visits garment factory; Japanese visitors, 1949; members of the Burma Labor Study Mission, 10/20/53
- Vladeck, B. Charney - selected (Box 44, Folder 21)
  Includes: group of men including David Dubinsky, Vladeck, and LaGuardia, 1/11/35
- Vladeck, B. Charney (Box 44, Folder 22)
  Includes: Vladeck memorial, with David Dubinsky and LaGuardia, 12/11/38
- Voting - selected (Box 45, Folder 1)
  Includes: women hold signs urging people to vote; Spanish sign on truck urging people to register to vote; David Dubinsky at the voting center
- Voting (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Includes: woman leads a group in song at the Voter Registration Rally; David Dubinsky - speech with sign in background urging voter registration; women on parade float; women with their voter registration cards; sign on truck urging people to register to vote
- Wagner, Robert - selected (Box 45, Folder 3)
  Includes: Benjamin Kaplan and Gus Tyler with Wagner, 10/10/56; Wagner and David Dubinsky
- Wagner, Robert (Box 45, Folder 4)
  Includes: Wagner - speech, David Dubinsky in background; group photo including Wagner, 1969; Wagner shakes garment worker`s hand, 1969; Wagner shakes hands with a black man; ILGWU political billboard endorsing Wagner; David Dubinsky speaks at Garment Center rally for Wagner, 11/2/61; Wagner and David Dubinsky; Wagner uses a cutter, 1969; Wagner and David Dubinsky riding bicycles down the streets of New York
- Washington - selected (Box 45, Folder 5)
  Includes: Sidney Hillman and David Dubinsky
- Washington (Box 45, Folder 6)
  Includes: Dave Beck before the AFL-CIO Ethical Practices Committee, with David Dubinsky, Arthur Goldberg, and A.J. Hayes, 9/5/57; David Dubinsky, 8/24/62
- West Coast - selected (Box 45, Folder 7)
  Includes: Leon Shapiro signs a contract as Isidor Stenzor of the ILGWU looks on, Los Angeles
- West Coast (Box 45, Folder 8)
  Includes: Louis Levy, L. Rubin, M.R. Naylor, and H. Golub talk, Los Angeles; Louis Levy shows Feiga Mendzyrzecka around Los Angeles office
- Whalen - selected (Box 45, Folder 9)
  Includes: Whalen speech; David Dubinsky and Whalen in front of a NRA sign
- Willkie, Wendell - selected (Box 45, Folder 10)
  Includes: Wendell Wilkie and David Dubinsky
- Willkie, Wendell (Box 45, Folder 11)
  Includes: Wilkie upon his return from Russia, 1945
- With These Hands - selected (Box 45, Folder 12)
  Includes: Scenes from the movie
- With These Hands [folder 1 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 13)
  Includes: Scenes from the movie; women in Tokyo meet to see the movie; William E. Moran and J. Van Connigem in front of an ILGWU display at opening of With These Hands; David Dubinsky and Sam Levene
- With These Hands [folder 2 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 14)
- With These Hands [folder 3 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 15)
- With These Hands [folder 4 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 16)
- With These Hands [folder 5 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 17)
- With These Hands [folder 6 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 18)
- With These Hands [folder 7 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 19)
- With These Hands [folder 8 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 20)
- With These Hands [folder 9 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 21)
- With These Hands [folder 10 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 22)
- With These Hands [folder 11 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 23)
- With These Hands [folder 12 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 24)
- With These Hands [folder 13 of 13] (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Womens Trade Union League (WTUL) - selected (Box 45, Folder 26)
  Includes: Eleanor Roosevelt, Rose Schneiderman, and Pauline Newman in group with Women's Trade Union League sign; members march in Labor Day parade, 1913. (see also box 30 ff 24 and box 40 ff 10-15)
- Workmens Circle (Box 45, Folder 27)
  Includes: David Dubinsky speech at Workmen`s Circle Home Dedication, 6/11/61, with Nelson Rockefeller; large crowd at the Dedication; David Dubinsky and Potofsky at the 75th Anniversary of Workmen's Circle, 11/16/76
- World War II - selected (Box 45, Folder 28)
  Includes: crowd scene, Field Hospital Tent rally; ILGWU Scrap metal drive; at launching of S.S. Morris Sigman, 2/2/44; David Dubinsky, Hochman, Vanni Montana, Jay Lovestone, John Jelo, and Antonini; Negotiating Committee from Rice - Stix, St. James, Missouri, Local 389
- World War II [folder 1 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 29)
  Includes: Matthew Woll drives an army truck, with David Dubinsky, Joseph Breslaw, and Israel Feinberg; women march in parade; ILGWU parade float; Hochman and Antonini in front of symbol for Victory Loan, 1945; crowd scene, Field Hospital Tent rally; man speaks in front of religious unity billboard; David Dubinsky speech; David Dubinsky at German Refugee Camps, 1958; children; Prime Minister of Israel David Ben Gurion at inauguration of Mapai Printing Press, 5/1/53; wreath at grave of war casualties; David Dubinsky at dinner of the Board of Trustees of the Refugee Relief Fund, 11/5/42; people holding war bonds; David Dubinsky gives speech after Pearl Harbor, Dec. 1942; sailors and women; women pack cans in boxes; dancing in London during the war; Ambassador John Winant - speech, 7/23/42; David Dubinsky laughs with ILGWU members and a sailor
- World War II [folder 2 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 30)
- World War II [folder 3 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 31)
- World War II (see also: Bx. 50 ff. 27) [folder 1 of 5] (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Includes: Line at Manhattan Blood Bank; Frances Day and Pat Taylor visit the Merchant Navy Club in London, 7/23/42; V.J. day in the Garment District; Local 142 gives toilet kits to veterans in hospital, St. Albans, New York, 4/3/43; Ernest Bevin looks at plaque for Rest Break House, England; Queen Elizabeth visits the Navy Club; Russian sailors with woman; South Jersey Joint Board manager gets a metal for war bond contributions; men play pool at the merchant navy club; women give "V" sign as they hold a poster for Victory Loans; men at the merchant navy club; woman with AFL war poster; Frances Day at Merchant Navy Club; parade; ILGWU members are taught first aid; women sew a flag, Local 65, Los Angeles; man shows how to tie parachute harness; women at garden at Rest Break House
- World War II (see also: Bx. 50 ff. 27) [folder 2 of 5] (Box 46, Folder 2)
- World War II (see also: Bx. 50 ff. 27) [folder 3 of 5] (Box 46, Folder 3)
- World War II (see also: Bx. 50 ff. 27) [folder 4 of 5] (Box 46, Folder 4)
- World War II (see also: Bx. 50 ff. 27) [folder 5 of 5] (Box 46, Folder 5)
- World War II - Liberty Ships Launching (Baltimore) - selected (Box 46, Folder 6)
  Includes: the ship "Benjamin Schlesinger"; at the "Morris Hillquit" ship launching; launching of "Meyer London"; brother of Meyer London at ship's launching
- World War II - Liberty Ships Launching (Baltimore) [folder 1 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 7)
  Includes: David Dubinsky, Zimmerman, and Hochman in group at ship launching; the ship "Morris Hillquit"; woman breaking bottle of champagne at Hillquit launching; Hillquit in the dry docks
- World War II - Liberty Ships Launching (Baltimore) [folder 2 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 8)
- World War II and Red Cross - selected (Box 46, Folder 9)
  Includes: Hochman gives David Dubinsky a check for $500,000 for War Relief Fund; Local 22 British - Russian medical aid fund; David Dubinsky, Green, Mr. Willis, Mrs. Morris Sigman, and Charles Kreindler
- World War II and Red Cross [folder 1 of 4] (Box 46, Folder 10)